No BS. The last post, I literally posted two seconds before I pulled up and looked out the
window to see helicopters. When I arrived at Tougaloo, there were seven police officers
standing there. And I was like, you know, I don't feel comfortable with this. And they said,
well, we here for you. And I said to them, are y'all security or police? And one of them said,
we police. She was just way too hyped to be 12. I said, nah, I don't F with police. And the person
who was there, the policeman who was there, I guess, as their representative, he was like, no,
come on now. I was like, no, I really, I don't F with police. I don't, I don't fuck with police.
So y'all are relieved of your duties. And they was like, all right. So I just want y'all to know,
if you ever see me anywhere surrounded by police, just know I have been compromised and they are
not there to protect me. They are there to keep me from running. Help me. I want to thank all of
the people at Mississippi for a Just World and Tougaloo College for really just showing me such
a beautiful time today on campus and giving me the opportunity to speak to so many listening voices
of all different ages, genders, classes, you name it. It was really just a beautiful time. And big ups
to Black With No Chaser for also spending time with me as well.
How Black am I going to have to get? How Black, Black, Black, Black, Black,